gamesrepublic.com 2016-06-10

# Privacy policy - Play. Share. Earn. Join the revolution at Games Republic. - GamesRepublic.com

#### 

Games Republic Limited with its seat at Malta, address: Cobalt House, level 2, Notabile Road, Mriehel BKR 3000, Malta, VLT1432, mail: contact@gamesrepublic.com (the “ **Company** ”) protects personal data of users - both natural and legal entities - of www.gamesrepublic.com website (the “ **Website** ”).

By using the Website and its content the Company may collect and process personal data of its users solely for purposes which are necessary to define, change, terminate and proper realization of activities, services and products available on the Website as regards user’s activity and orders on the Website. The Company may use personal data for marketing, information or other purposes (e.g. updates, contests, promotions, newsletters) solely upon user’s individual consent. 

Personal data shall be available only for entitled entities, on terms and in the scope defined by this Privacy Police, agreements concluded with user and binding regulations of law. Each person or entity shall be entitled to access, correct, actualization and removal of its personal data. If during use of the Website user submits Company any personal data, the Company shall be deemed administrator of said personal data. The Company’s privacy policy does not cover external websites or any third party activity. 

The purpose of this Privacy Policy is to ensure safety of personal data of users of the Website, in particular prevention against any unauthorized used by any third party. Access to personal database shall be granted only to persons or entities authorised by the Company as database administrator. The Company shall take any safety measurements which shall prevent personal data against its loss or usage by unauthorized persons, in particular by using proper technical equipment, and possibility of defining levels of safety. The Company ensures realization of regulations concerning personal data protection, as well as stipulate possibility of access, actualization, removal and notification of objections in the scope of personal data. 

Information concerning computer’s IP, domain, type of browser and operational system shall be automatically collected during each visit of user on the Website. All data collected in this manner shall be accessed solely by the Company, and shall not be in any manner distributed to any third party. Such data shall be used only for visit statistics in order to improve website’s functionality. Data collected automatically during each visit shall not be changed or removed. The Company within its website shall use cookies files to identification of user in order to improve website’s functionality and correctness. Cookies files shall not download any personal data of user’s visiting website, while such user is allowed to change cookies files settings in his/her internet browser in order to exclude receiving or sending cookies files. The Company informs and warns that such modification in cookies files settings in internet browser in the scope necessary for certification process, safety or maintaining user’s preferences, might result in difficulties in usage of Company’s Website by user or in extreme circumstances might render impossible to usage of such website, depending on type of user’s settings and type of internet browser. 

The Company reserves right to amend this Privacy Policy by its republishing or publish its amended version.
